Guide to the Football Game Film Collection, 1934-2007 UA.13.01.0004
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Football Game Films
  - Tennessee, 1973 September 15
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Third Quarter, 1973 September 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 91, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0978)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Fourth Quarter, 1973 September 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 91, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0979)
  - Washington, 1973 September 22
    Duke win, score: 23-21
    - Duke vs. Washington: First Quarter, 1973 September 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 92, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0980)
    - Duke vs. Washington: Second Quarter, 1973 September 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 92, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0981)
    - Duke vs. Washington: Third Quarter, 1973 September 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 92, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0982)
    - Duke vs. Washington: Fourth Quarter, 1973 September 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 92, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0983)
  - Virginia, 1973 September 29
    - Duke vs. Virginia: First Quarter, 1973 September 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 92, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0984)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Second Quarter, 1973 September 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 92, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0985)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Third Quarter, 1973 September 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 92, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0986)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Fourth Quarter, 1973 September 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 92, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0987)
  - Purdue, 1973 October 06
    - Duke vs. Purdue: First Quarter, 1973 October 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 92, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0988)
    - Duke vs. Purdue: Second Quarter, 1973 October 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 92, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0989)
    - Duke vs. Purdue: Third Quarter, 1973 October 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 92, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0990)
    - Duke vs. Purdue: Fourth Quarter, 1973 October 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 92, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0991)
  - Tulane, 1973 October 13
    Duke loss, score: 17-24
    - Duke vs. Tulane: First Quarter, 1973 October 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 91, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0992)
    - Duke vs. Tulane: Second Quarter, 1973 October 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 91, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0993)
    - Duke vs. Tulane: Third Quarter, 1973 October 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 91, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0994)
    - Duke vs. Tulane: Fourth Quarter, 1973 October 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 91, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0995)
    - Duke vs. Tulane: Unknown game film coverage, 1973 October 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0996)
  - Clemson, 1973 October 20
    Duke loss, score: 8-24
    - Duke vs. Clemson: First Quarter, 1973 October 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 93, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0997)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Second Quarter, 1973 October 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 93, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0998)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Third Quarter, 1973 October 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 93, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0999)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Fourth Quarter, 1973 October 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 93, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1000)
  - Maryland, 1973 October 27
    Duke loss, score: 10-30
    - Duke vs. Maryland: First Quarter, 1973 October 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 93, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1001)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Second Quarter, 1973 October 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 93, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1002)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Third Quarter, 1973 October 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 93, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1003)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Fourth Quarter, 1973 October 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 93, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1004)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Unknown game film coverage, 1973 October 27; DVD
  - Georgia Tech, 1973 November 03
    Duke loss, score: 10-12
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: First Quarter, 1973 November 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 93, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1005)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Second Quarter, 1973 November 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 93, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1006)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Third Quarter, 1973 November 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 93, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1007)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Fourth Quarter, 1973 November 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 93, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1008)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unknown game film coverage, 1973 November 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1009)
  - Wake Forest, 1973 November 10
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: First Quarter, 1973 November 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 93, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1010)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Second Quarter, 1973 November 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 93, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1011)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Third Quarter, 1973 November 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 93, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1012)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Fourth Quarter, 1973 November 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 93, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1013)
  - NC State, 1973 November 17
    Duke loss, score: 3-21
    - Duke vs. NC State: Unknown game film coverage, 1973 November 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1014)
  - North Carolina, 1973 November 24
    Duke win, score: 27-10
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: First Quarter, 1973 November 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 94, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1015)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Second Quarter, 1973 November 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 94, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1016)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Third Quarter, 1973 November 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 94, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1017)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Fourth Quarter, 1973 November 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 94, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1018)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unknown game film coverage, 1973 November 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1019)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unknown game film coverage, 1973 November 24; DVD
  - Highlights, 1974 September 01 - 1974 December 31
    - Highlights, 1974 September 01 - 1974 December 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1020)
    - Highlights, 1974 September 01 - 1974 December 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1021)
  - NC State, 1974 September 14
    Duke loss, score: 21-35
    - Duke vs. NC State: Offense 1, 1974 September 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1022)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Offense 2, 1974 September 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1023)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Defense 1, 1974 September 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1024)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Defense 2, 1974 September 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1025)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Offense 1, 1974 September 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1026)
  - South Carolina, 1974 September 21
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Offense 1, 1974 September 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1027)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Offense 2, 1974 September 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1028)
  - Virginia, 1974 September 28
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Offense 1, 1974 September 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1029)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Offense 2, 1974 September 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1030)
  - Purdue, 1974 October 05
    - Duke vs. Purdue: First Quarter, 1974 October 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1031)
    - Duke vs. Purdue: Second Quarter, 1974 October 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1032)
    - Duke vs. Purdue: Third Quarter, 1974 October 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1033)
    - Duke vs. Purdue: Fourth Quarter, 1974 October 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1034)
  - Clemson, 1974 October 19
    Duke loss, score: 13 - 17
    - Duke vs. Clemson: First Quarter, 1974 October 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1035)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Second Quarter, 1974 October 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1036)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Third Quarter, 1974 October 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1037)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Fourth Quarter, 1974 October 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1038)
  - Florida, 1974 October 26
    Duke loss, score: 13-30
    - Duke vs. Florida: Offense 1, 1974 October 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1039)
    - Duke vs. Florida: Offense 2, 1974 October 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1040)
    - Duke vs. Florida: Defense 1, 1974 October 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1041)
    - Duke vs. Florida: Defense 2, 1974 October 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1042)
  - Georgia Tech, 1974 November 02
    Duke win, score: 9-0
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: First Quarter, 1974 November 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1043)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Second Quarter, 1974 November 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1044)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Third Quarter, 1974 November 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1045)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Fourth Quarter, 1974 November 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1046)
  - Wake Forest, 1974 November 09
    Duke win, score: 23-7
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Defense 1, 1974 November 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1047)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Defense 2, 1974 November 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1048)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Offense 1, 1974 November 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1049)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Offense 2, 1974 November 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1050)
  - Maryland, 1974 November 16
    Duke loss, score: 13-56
    - Duke vs. Maryland: First Quarter, 1974 November 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1051)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Second Quarter, 1974 November 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1052)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Third Quarter, 1974 November 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1053)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Fourth Quarter, 1974 November 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1054)
  - North Carolina, 1974 November 23
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Offense 1, 1974 November 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1055)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Offense 2, 1974 November 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1056)
  - USC, 1975 September 12
    Duke loss, score: 7-35
    - Duke vs. USC: First Quarter, 1975 September 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1057)
    - Duke vs. USC: Second Quarter, 1975 September 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1058)
    - Duke vs. USC: Third Quarter, 1975 September 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1059)
    - Duke vs. USC: Fourth Quarter, 1975 September 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1060)
    - Duke vs. USC: Unknown game film coverage, 1975 September 12; DVD
  - South Carolina, 1975 September 20
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: First Quarter, 1975 September 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1061)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Second Quarter, 1975 September 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1062)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Third Quarter, 1975 September 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1063)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Fourth Quarter, 1975 September 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1064)
  - Virginia, 1975 September 27
    Duke win, score: 26-11
    - Duke vs. Virginia: First Quarter, 1975 September 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1065)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Second Quarter, 1975 September 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1066)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Third Quarter, 1975 September 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1067)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Fourth Quarter, 1975 September 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1068)
  - Pitt, 1975 October 04
    - Duke vs. Pitt: Reel 1, 1975 October 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1069)
    - Duke vs. Pitt: Reel 2, 1975 October 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1070)
    - Duke vs. Pitt: Reel 3, 1975 October 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1071)
    - Duke vs. Pitt: Offense 1, 1975 October 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1072)
    - Duke vs. Pitt: Offense 2, 1975 October 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1073)
    - Duke vs. Pitt: Defense 1, 1975 October 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1074)
    - Duke vs. Pitt: Defense 2, 1975 October 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1075)
    - Duke vs. Pitt: Kick, 1975 October 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1076)
    - Duke vs. Pitt: Unknown game film coverage, 1975 October 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1077)
  - Army, 1975 October 11
    - Duke vs. Army: Reel 1, 1975 October 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1078)
    - Duke vs. Army: Reel 2, 1975 October 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1079)
    - Duke vs. Army: Reel 3, 1975 October 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1080)
    - Duke vs. Army: Reel 4, 1975 October 11 (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1081)
    - Duke vs. Army: Unknown game film coverage, 1975 October 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 136, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1082)
  - Clemson, 1975 October 18
    Duke win, score: 25-21
    - Duke vs. Clemson: First Quarter, 1975 October 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1083)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Second Quarter, 1975 October 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1084)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Third Quarter, 1975 October 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1085)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Fourth Quarter, 1975 October 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1086)
  - Florida, 1975 October 25
    - Duke vs. Florida: Reel 1, 1975 October 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1087)
    - Duke vs. Florida: Reel 2, 1975 October 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1088)
    - Duke vs. Florida: Reel 3, 1975 October 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1089)
    - Duke vs. Florida: Offense 1, 1975 October 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1090)
    - Duke vs. Florida: Defense 1, 1975 October 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1091)
    - Duke vs. Florida: Defense 1, 1975 October 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1092)
    - Duke vs. Florida: Offense 2, 1975 October 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1093)
    - Duke vs. Florida: Kick, 1975 October 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1094)
  - Georgia Tech, 1975 November 01
    Duke win, score: 6-21
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 1, 1975 November 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1095)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 2, 1975 November 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1096)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 3, 1975 November 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1097)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Defense 1, 1975 November 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1098)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Defense 2, 1975 November 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1099)
  - Wake Forest, 1975 November 08
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1975 November 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1100)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1975 November 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1101)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1975 November 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1102)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1975 November 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1103)
  - NC State, 1975 November 15
    Duke T, score: 21-21
    - Duke vs. NC State: Offense 1, 1975 November 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1104)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Offense 2, 1975 November 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1105)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Kick, 1975 November 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1106)
  - North Carolina, 1975 November 22
    Duke T, score: 17-17
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Kick, 1975 November 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1107)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1975 November 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1108)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1975 November 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1109)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1975 November 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1110)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Offense 1, 1975 November 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1111)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Offense 2, 1975 November 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1112)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Defense 1, 1975 November 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1113)
  - Tennessee, 1976 September 11
    Duke win, score: 21-18
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: First Quarter, 1976 September 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1114)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Second Quarter, 1976 September 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1115)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Third Quarter, 1976 September 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1116)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Fourth Quarter, 1976 September 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1117)
  - South Carolina, 1976 September 18
    Duke loss, score: 6-24
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: First Quarter, 1976 September 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1118)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Second Quarter, 1976 September 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1119)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Third Quarter, 1976 September 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1120)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Fourth Quarter, 1976 September 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1121)
  - Virginia, 1976 September 25
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Defense 1, 1976 September 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1122)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Offense 1, 1976 September 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1123)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Offense 2, 1976 September 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1124)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: First Quarter, 1976 September 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1125)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Third Quarter, 1976 September 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1126)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Fourth Quarter, 1976 September 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1127)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Defense 2, 1976 September 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1604)
  - Pitt, 1976 October 02
    Duke loss, score: 31-44
    - Duke vs. Pitt: Defense 1, 1976 October 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1128)
    - Duke vs. Pitt: Defense 2, 1976 October 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1129)
  - Miami, 1976 October 09
    - Duke vs. Miami: First Quarter, 1976 October 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1130)
    - Duke vs. Miami: Second Quarter, 1976 October 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1131)
    - Duke vs. Miami: Third Quarter, 1976 October 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1132)
    - Duke vs. Miami: Fourth Quarter, 1976 October 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1133)
  - Clemson, 1976 October 16
    Duke T, score: 18-18
    - Duke vs. Clemson: First Quarter, 1976 October 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1134)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Second Quarter, 1976 October 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1135)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Third Quarter, 1976 October 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1136)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Defense 1, 1976 October 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1137)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Defense 2, 1976 October 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1138)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Offense 1, 1976 October 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1139)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Offense 2, 1976 October 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1140)
  - Maryland, 1976 October 23
    Duke loss, score: 3-30
    - Duke vs. Maryland: First Quarter, 1976 October 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1141)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Second Quarter, 1976 October 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1142)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Third Quarter, 1976 October 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1143)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Fourth Quarter, 1976 October 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1144)
  - Georgia Tech, 1976 October 30
    Duke win, score: 31-7
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: First Quarter, 1976 October 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1145)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Second Quarter, 1976 October 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1146)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Third Quarter, 1976 October 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1147)
  - Wake Forest, 1976 November 06
    Duke loss, score: 17-38
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: First Quarter, 1976 November 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1148)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Second Quarter, 1976 November 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1149)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Third Quarter, 1976 November 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1150)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Fourth Quarter, 1976 November 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1151)
  - NC State, 1976 November 13
    Duke win, score: 28 - 14
    - Duke vs. NC State: Defense 1, 1976 November 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 9, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1152)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Defense 2, 1976 November 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 9, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1153)
  - North Carolina, 1976 November 20
    Duke loss, score: 38-39
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: First Quarter, 1976 November 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 9, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1154)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Second Quarter, 1976 November 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 9, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1155)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Second Quarter, 1976 November 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 9, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1156)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Fourth Quarter, 1976 November 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 9, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1157)
  - Georgia Tech, 1979 November 03
    Duke loss, score: 14-24
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: First Quarter, 1979 November 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 10, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1158)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Second Quarter, 1979 November 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 10, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1159)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Third Quarter, 1979 November 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 10, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1160)